Father?
What?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Go to sleep.
No!
Go to sleep.
It has nothing to do.
He does not believe.
Why we do not see.
It's time to tell him.
It is connected all day on that thing. He
​​does not listen. I'm a failure as a father.
- You are very bitter.
- Go. Talk to him.
Take it easy, okay?
Mati?
Can I talk to you?
I'm sleeping. Tomorrow.
Left the game on.
Look. It's a difficult play.
How'd you do that? What did you do?
Show me!
I was not sleeping?
We need to talk.
Feel free.
I'll tell you a story.
You have to use your imagination.
This happened not long ago
in a town right near here
Where a square as our
There was a statue of the founder, as our
had a bar like ours
Come on, Eusebio.
A transcendental number
whose value is the ratio
high on any circumference to its diameter.
- Two letters.
- Pi.
Come on, Eusebio.
What is the last name of the
famous playwright William...
Pi.
A little boy like you,
worked in this place .
- I'm not a little boy.
- Amadeo, hurry, little boy
I'm not a little boy.
This boy had a weakness
Weakness? It's not like I
Hello, Amadeo.
Hi!
I love ice cream.
Like?
Of course I do.
Laurita has a boyfriend!
Dual Axis!
Laurita Look what you did to me!
Can I show you my team?
I'd love to see.
'll See how it goes.
- I was tired of the same players.
- Now is different?
- There are now special.
- And gorgeous!
The Lettuce dribbles the ball.
The number five is on fire.
He has the rhythm of the tropics
Blood
Igor catches the ball. Cool as ice.
A blockage in the endzone
He kicks and is locked
He dribbles the opponent...
Hits the wall and . in your head
Lots of tension in the air. The Octopus
is asking for the password
Drastic! A fine pass
It opens to the side with the Korean
Lee Park
The silence is deafening
Go to surprise Cordobes
ball effect. El Loco, poet, receives
Short Pass Beto
The most charismatic player continent
raises its head
and sees Captain
unique, unmatched, my friend Capi .
Pass straight through the keeper
Goal!
Yes! Goal!
They were a plain shirt.
No matter. Are the plain shirt.
Look! This is new.
See.
I want to play with you too.
Want to play with me.
- He wants too.
-It's yours!
Hey, you,
'm talking to you.
Do not want to play with me?
Is the famous boy with foosball?
He is silent and shy?
If it's so good, play with me.
No.
Are you afraid?
Play with it.
Come, Amadeo, please.
For me.
Please Amadeo. I beg.
I beg. Knees. He will play.
Come on. I do not have all day.
He is focusing.
The champion has a coach.
Goal!
Other! Not seen this.
The statue stood.
The team started well.
Is a game of many goals.
The attack from the left.
Goal! Goal for the team plain shirt.
Come on! Please.
Poor little chick.
Whether the mother hen?
Let's make the chicken.
Sergio goes to Gonzalo, Gonzalo
for Jorge, Jorge to...
Goal!
Is my champion! Goal!
Quickly. Put the ball.
Come on!
Another goal Champion!
'Goal!
"No
We are tied.
No tie.
As you wish.
Go.
That's it!
Yeah, Amadeo! Champion!
! The game is not over.
I want to win.
I want coins.
Give me more balls. Let me go.
I want to win. I always win.
I want to win.
Yes!
Damn town! I hate!
It's your fault for having founded Ia.
I hate you.
- I hate you.
- Hey kid.
What do you want?
Do not like to lose?
Come on, Eusebio. And this?
River in northern Italy. Two letters.
Pi.
What? Do not understand us?
Come on! Anyone want to play?
Eusebio. One more. Please.
Double Axle, how about a rematch?
- Hi, Amadeus.
-Hello.
So?
- Okay?
- Everything.
Want to play?
We're too old for foosball.
Look.
Look at this.
'm Leaving, Amadeo.
Where?
For the city, studying. Save ¡
for five years because it is expensive.
I'll spend it all,
but I will have a future, Amadeo.
The Greeks, the Romans, even a Swiss.
I will be part of history, Amadeo.
What do you say?
What I'm...
Very proud of you.
What will you do?
Well, you know, I...
I am involved in a thousand things.
My head is full of ideas.
I am involved in the theme of...
Some players are
helping me and...
has a communication problem
in midfield, lacking something,
and I'm developing
Technique triple wind mill.
Yeah, I...
A lot.
Amadeo can not think of a future if you
stay the whole time playing foosball.
Good afternoon to you, dear neighbors
this beloved city.
Happiness for everyone, no more sorrow.
We are here to announce the
opening of Universal Astro Ball.
Yes, here,
a sports venture that will
attract tourists to this city
and bring money into their pockets.
Universal Astro Ball,
conceived, planned and funded by
be a wonderful
for whom this city has been
mother and father.
A true hometown hero.
Technical...
Do not fear. We're not here to attack them.
Do not be afraid. We're friends.
He was just an ordinary boy
when caught.
The superstar international football
Ezekiel Remacho EI Grosso.
Thank you, my small town,
by this wonderful reception.
Many years passed,
but never forgotten.
My small town, I'm happy to say that
our lives will be connected forever.
Why keep saying "my little town"?
Obvious. It is small and, moreover,
is mine.
As well, their?
Let's talk to the mayor.
Course. Mayor.
Talk later!
Bye, mayor. We do not need you.
Welcome to the new city.
A clear homage to the noblest of sports,
with the largest stadium in the world.
Tours.
Theme parks.
And a museum dedicated to the
most important person in history.
We do not want stadium here.
I have never forgotten you.
Or you.
Construction will begin today
and let's get this bar.
No.
No. Stop it!
Get out. Fast!
Stop them, please.
Impossible. You can not stop progress.
Sali, come on.
I want a rematch.
Wait. Can not do this to us.
Is a city is its people.
My City. Its people.
All this because of a game of foosball?
Please, of course not.
Bring me the foosball table
or not to return.
Please wait.
The city is always right.
Well, the city almost always right.
Please listen to me.
Please . I will not leave you
alone until you hear me.
I'm all ears.
What is this? No. Do not press the buttons.
Laura! Laura! Laura!
Laura!
Amadeo?
Hey, Amadeo?
I'm here.
Amadeo.
Capi, are you?
Of course I am. Who else?
What is this guy? We are brothers or not?
3.724 were unbeaten matches.
What about?
This is a nightmare.
I'll wake up and everything will be fine.
The bar, my foosball table.
No.
Is not a nightmare.
No. Do not be discouraged now.
Do not be discouraged when
we can still turn it around.
- Are you kidding?
- Not!
- You have to animate and attack.
- Animate Me? What are you talking about?
I threw my life away playing
foosball and now I have nothing.
As well, it has nothing?
- Come here because you have more...
- Leave me alone.
Please stop, Amadeo.
Do not move, I have short legs.
I am a useless and now
Laura goes away and I...
I can not do anything,
I have nothing to hold Ia.
On top, I'm talking to
a piece of lead and think it's normal.
- Okay. Finished?
- Yes
I am not a piece of lead.
I'm left-winger and captain of
the best team Foosball World
and you are the undefeated champion.
Has unerring vision, perfect
balance and a supreme wrist.
Can not remember the
challenge with the neighbor?
He was destroying us and laughing at us.
Remember how he laughed?
- He was laughing at you as well.
-No. He did not laugh like that.
- He laughed as well.
-No.
- As he laughed, then?
- Like a squirrel. So...
And your friend who laughed...
- It is.
-'S.
We were losing 3-0 and turned to
4-3.
Amadeo, we are unbeatable.
The two of us together.
We do not need anyone else.
Come behind the faces made of iron.
Women come and go.
Do you think they come from?
Let her go, if you want.
If we have the whole team,
we fear no one.
We do what we must do, as with the
Gobero, Amadeo.
4 through 3. 4 A 3!
Do not need anyone. Nobody.
Not the city,
or the neighborhood,
or Laura...
No.
I need Laura.
And you will have Ia.
With the full team,
EI Grosso will not have a chance. 'll See.
-
Yes - Let's call the boys.
- Where?
- I do not know.
Inside foosball,
I know everything, but out here,
-'m lost.
- I know!
- Trash.
- Garbage.
Where is the trash?
I went. At the municipal deposit.
- The deposit!
- Let IA.
Even have defeated the
Gobero by 4-3, Amadeo?
Goals Beto, Loco and two mine.
Do not remember?
- His second was a corner.
- No. It was lateral.
- Where are we going?
- Nothing special, my summer home.
Hold on tight.
- I do not like that.
- It's pretty cool.
How so? I do this all day.
And the best part is yet to come.
Please do not!
Can you tell me how we will find them here?
Walkthrough.
Let's calm down, roll up their sleeves
and  start
Wow! What a crazy trip.
Is. That's it!
The field got bigger.
Beto, Beto!
I'm out!
Help!
Not!
Saw what Bob did?
Are you Beto!
Loco! Beto!
- Capi!
- Good to see you.
You have no idea how the
separation was difficult.
Look at this. How about?
Beto want to do this.
He wants to break free.
Olé! We are the champions
Okay, come on.
- Spin, spin. Watch the hair.
- I'm free.
I'm free as the morning sun.
I am free.
How wonderful!
Bob has always been a great scorer.
Now, brace yourselves.
Goalscorer? I score goals, Beto.
Yes, Capi. Sorry. Beto was confused.
Great scorer.
Leave . I think it's crazy.
I hear. Again, I'm the scorer.
No. Really?
A mouse ate your brain?
Everyone knows that Bob has
always been the goal scorer.
And it's hard to be the scorer
this useless team.
As well, pointless team?
If I do not pass the ball,
all are lost.
- He hit his head.
-I'll hit your head, buck.
- I am the scorer.
- You better hold me.
Do not tease me.
I'm saying. Do not tease me.
- I'm that milestone goals.
- No, no.
Boys! This is not good for the sport.
We need to be united.
Aligned with the universe.
Is a goalscorer rainbow.
Need an ambulance to take this crazy guy.
- Go get you after I give you a way.
- Do not tease me.
- I'm serious.
- Get away from me.
Not even come close, but...
Enough ¡
We are alone, guys.
You are all I have left.
Amadeo.
I knew the tears
are mourning the soul
at sea of ​​existence?
- What did he say?
- Who Is Grieving?
- Loco. Why do not you shut up?
- Do not tell me to shut up.
Look...
Let's not confuse us. The sensitivity
is one thing and stupidity is another.
Stupidity is what you're saying now.
Shut up.
- Be quiet.
- Are interfering.
Bob is the scorer.
You guys are pathetic.
Straight?
- Lisandro, burgundy suits you well.
- Maroon.
You are beautiful. Straightened hair?
Now it is full of garbage here.
Why not get closer and say that
?
Have you asked politely.
I mean it in your face
30 years ago.
What is the problem? Are you afraid?
The mouse ate the tongue?
No, but maybe eat her.
- Show no fear.
- Look who's talking.
Come on!
Over there.
No. Beto did not enter.
Not!
Poor Beto.
The led and not defend.
- Not worth nothing.
- Not worthless.
E're worth everything.
What?
Do not listen. He thus speaks poor thing.
We have to go.
We can not stay in this house forever.
Is, the owner may appear.
Beto, Beto, Betito, Betito.
Know he was our top scorer, no?
He was our scorer.
And the best teammate.
Very humble.
Always thinking of others.
Poor Beto.
Capi. Beto has become
one with the universe.
When our time comes, we find
Io and'll be three.
With the universe?
With the universe, we are four.
So, with all, gives 12.
Let's put the universe on the bench
and start winning again.
Hey guys!
What are you doing there?
Get down, your buck.
Calm, animal.
E?
Felt the lack of Beto, right?
Please?
Who could miss?
Why he treats you like that?
Because otherwise he rides.
Do not see what you did with the mouse?
Where will the Amadeo is?
Look.
Left.
Left. Right.
Forward.
Back . Forward. Ali
We found him.
Go.
- They are taking.
- Look IA.
Come on, I do not know his name.
Quickly. We do not have all night.
Ew!
"I want foosball."
The things I do for him.
What are you doing, you idiot?
The idiot is dead and dangerous arrived.
Remember me!
My name is Amadeo.
Just saw? He was gone. Did it all myself.
No one is completely alone.
He was afraid.
Even I was scared of me.
Very cute. It was very good.
Now let's find the others.
Not!
Stay down.
Come on, pet.
No, Beto.
Do not do it again. Come back.
What are you doing?
Go look for it.
He did not give you your best self?
Ungrateful. Your rata.
Look. Your hair leave a trail.
Let's follow.
Bye, Claret. Looks like we have to go.
- Go leave me here?
- Has another plan?
- I do not think. 'm Pure feeling.
- Apparently Lisito.
- You have to stay here. Goodbye.
- Great.
And if you do not take me,
who will play against?
Welcome to my humble home.
What a beautiful statue.
I love abstract art.
Yes, yes.
I love this statue.
I admire your good taste.
Two of us.
- Come on.
- No, darling, this side here.
Tell him you are here on my behalf.
Calm, brother.
Things do not resolve well.
Wait.
With the crown jewels, not plays.
Do not you dare!
Stop it or rip your esophagus!
So many things still left me
to do in life!
I'm Korean!
Never even seen the sea.
And now
Boys! Here!
Bob, are you?
No, Beto left.
He left a message.
He loves all of you.
Get out of there. What are you doing?
Bob is not here.
Bob is gone.
Calm, friend.
Force
Force, Beto.
Bob did what he could.
Do not worry, brother.
They cut my hair.
I understand. The failure also hurt me.
But you're used to.
This will be impossible.
There's no way to find him.
It is better if we split up.
That's right, Captain. Divide and conquer.
's How it works.
- Tulio said that.
- Need to share the opponents, Loco.
- Tulio said.
- Stop that Tulio. Who cares?
Not!
Amadeo! Please!
Look what they did with us.
Hey, stop! Come back here.
Come on. You, I do not know his name.
Come with me.
Malpas.
Malpas. What have they done to you?
- Go, Capi. Save yourself while you can.
- No. I'm not leaving without you.
- Where's your brother?
- What brother?
How so?
Where's the other Malparitti?
Him .. Ali
- Ali? Not seeing.
-'Ll See soon.
- Malpas, hold my hand.
- No, hold my.
Not!
Beto feels hurt.
- Unable to continue.
- Come on.
Cactus complains of dry?
And still itches.
Come tingle.
I'm falling, Malpas. I can not...
Grab yourself. Has no team without you.
Goodbye, brother.
Thanks for giving me a hand, but
is too slippery.
How could you leave him fall, animal?
You worthless.
Say it to my face.
- I say to your face, quadruped.
- Draught, bipedal.
- Hold the legs.
- I can not reach.
Do not yell. It's okay.
Okay? Look down.
- What do we do now?
- That's why I'm crying.
In this case, continue.
Please get me out and take me home.
I look like a sheep?
Those idiots! Find them!
Do not overdo it.
- Talk right, Russian.
- Not really Chinese.
- I'm Korean.
- Okay!
May God bless you, brother.
Boys, calm. You can trust me.
Leave me alone!
- Having fun? Why not invite me?
- Bitter.
Awesome.
He ​​is even uglier up close.
If my hands were free...
Come on!
One, two, three...
- What are you doing? Are you crazy?
- Shut up, ugly.
're Right. He is ugly.
Do not mess with my brother.
About
you considered using as a garnish?
I'm not garnish. I'm a pin.
- What?
- That's right.
If you take me away, everything comes down.
What is the problem? Where do they go?
Do not go away. The best is yet to come.
Loco! Wait for us.
Courage, boys.
There has to be chance against
a team without arms and legs.
- Capi!
- Octopus!
- What have they done to you?
It's humiliating, Capi.
Made me burgundy.
Get out of there. Get him out of there.
Better dead than burgundy.
Cowards!
Not ashamed to cry with
unfortunate companions?
No companions, although
bastards.
- Who called the bastard?
- Were always there.
Do not make me laugh.
I'm tired of picking up your ball.
- My?
- No, my sister.
Whenever you trashed.
- It?
- You think you're good!
- You calling me names?
- Yes, your buck.
Enough ¡
Look where we are.
Look around you.
Not realize that what unites us is
more than what divides us?
From now on,
let's work together. Right?
Have something you admire him?
- It is...
I'm not listening.
- It is a good...-
Louder!
He is a good quarterback.
See how easy that was? Now, you. Come on.
It will not say what it is...
He is a great leader.
It is said that he is a great leader.
So what?
Lovely. We had a blast.
- We were afraid of you.
- From me?
You know we called you?
- Who, me?
- No, I do.
-
You. - No, you fool.
- Te we called "Buffalo".
- Really?
- Buffalo.
Truth.
It was impossible to stop you.
Do you remember the time we played
three hours without stopping?
I remember like it was yesterday.
Old Thumbtack was still alive.
It was tough, but as he drank.
In the end, was so drunk that made me
rotate and break a window.
I remember it!
And the guy wanted me to pay!
It was pretty funny.
- Where are they?
- Ali
We mix a classic with a
modern foosball foosball.
Give me the key.
Be careful, please!
Your hands are shaking, come on!
Now the lettuce is fresher.
Fresher?
Public Expensive
Bob came to say goodbye.
He will go on tour.
Do not be humble, please.
Even if you beg, Beto can not stand.
Look at the bright side.
Without being overshadowed by me,
could grow.
Let me go, Amadeo. I'll kill you.
Get this clown wig!
's Why Beto goes away.
In the theater, there is no jealousy.
There is no envy.
All is harmony and applause.
Amadeo.
Amadeo. Led the edges.
- They took my team and we are burgundy.
- We must rescue them.
Need them.
Let's keep looking.
Where are you going? Wait for me.
- Look who's here.
- Who?
- Amadeo.
- Well at the right time.
Wait for Beto. Do not let him here.
Come here, Bob.
Is this you?
Are you, Betito?
Bob will not leave you.
He ​​knows they need it.
Amadeo.
Throw the ball and we play a little.
When is it?
It's too far.
Amadeo. Look at this.
What?
Laura is in danger.
Forget Laura. We are all together.
Do not need it.
But she needs us.
She was, Amadeo. Forget.
Should have seen her face.
I know. Come on.
Please...
- Amadeo, women are...
- As mines.
Exactly.
Not going anywhere. You will?
- No, I'm right here.
- Beto is.
This is my place in the world.
See?
I feel...
- I feel something...
- Right here. In the fourth chakra.
I also. An empty.
Beto feels pain in the chest.
Beto...
It is a sadness.
Amadeo. Wait for us.
- We can keep looking if you want.
- Shut up, idiot!
At least I have something to
entertain this wayward boy.
For the mansion, dizzy.
Do not know how to start.
No key. Only buttons.
Relax. It blue.
- What is the problem, asshole?
- A problem with visibility.
- What's wrong with the window?
- I do not know. It does not work.
Yes, of course. It was blue.
The Green...
- The green, no.
- Why did you say it was green?
Do not let me finish.
I would say: "Green, no."
This is a tribute to my shoulders, where
carry all games.
Sure, you play alone.
Believed that force me to play with ten?
This regulation has to end.
- This is me, throwing the disc.
- A disc.
The decorator said the same thing.
Quanta ignorant people... My goodness!
This one always gets me.
Shows how frail I am like a child.
Good as a mother.
Simultaneously.
See! I'm creepy.
- And this?
- I do not know what this is doing.
- Come on.
- Not!
So? Like me, right?
Why are you doing this?
Got money. Has fame.
Has success.
Why not leave the city in peace?
I did not.
Do you like me or not?
We can not fight you.
You will always win. You have everything.
I have everything.
And not always won.
Once I lost. Do not you remember?
- I'm here.
- Right on time.
Come on.
Gimme that. I was looking for it.
Where are the others?
Useless leech. For support you?
Locate the rest.
Out!
- Dolls are harmless.
- Harmless?
They represent the only failure
of my life. Come on.
He is leading again! Not!
He is leading again!
- Here we are.
- There could have been?
Do not walk even ten
meters without sponsor.
- What is this?
- The future of sports and their stars.
The best of nature and science,
and nanotechnology muscles.
Perfection. Perfecting the perfect.
- And this?
- White pigeons.
A tame animal with a neutral attitude,
are not good for IBOPE.
These are pigeons 2.0.
Warring and loyal to the team.
Australian ostrich is the fastest
animal in the world with a deadly kick.
Imagine sneakers with
these characteristics?
- Give it to me.
- What will you do?
What would happen if I
mixed up this pile of crap
with this shoes?
- Stop, please.
Maybe I can boot
nails that make me stronger or at least
'll step on them for life.
Stop, please.
What will you do chinese?
He is Korean.
What will he do?
He's thinking.
Is another advantage we have
mixuruca about your team.
- They will see him. I do not understand.
- Obviously you do not understand.
You are dealing with a
master of oriental wisdom.
The guy can catch
things that you and I can not perceive.
Something that eludes
the rest of us mortals.
These numbers . I'm confused.
Always brute force, the strength stupid.
What are you doing?
This will not help.
Stop. Show more inventions.
Come. Inventions.
No, wait. Stop.
Let me go.
Is not how you do it.
Wow, that door hit me?
I have to teach you everything?
Ready?
Now!
What will you teach us?
There I go.
Stop!
Not!
Please! Release.
- I'm not doing anything with it.
- Leave her alone.
Do not mess with her.
Cai. And there?
Please, I beg you. Release.
Do not tell me you like this idiot.
And if I like it?
Not!
No.
I'll blow you
and with this filthy town!
- Over here, guys.
- Slowly.
Laura.
Watch the hair.
Come on.
What fauna is against Beto?
This is the worst preseason of my life.
- Do not give up now, Claret.
- Color Wine!
Capi!
Loco!
Not!
Never be afraid to fly!
- Gonna explode!
- Amadeo!
Bye.
I'm fine. Thank God I saved
the most valuable thing. Myself.
If you did nothing,
I would be the most affected. E...
- Okay?
- Everything. Are you all right, Laura?
Me? Alright.
I should not have done that, Amadeo.
He ​​is strong and well trained.
Should not have faced Io. It's crazy.
- I came to save you.
- It was wrong to do so.
I can handle myself.
You know I care about you.
- I thought if I came and...
- What do you think?
That I fall in love with you
for your courage, by face
a guy who is much stronger than you?
Is that what you thought?
A Time!
I ¡defeat once.
Everyone knows that I
have never lost anything.
Once and I challenge you to a rematch
publicly.
- Want to challenge me?
- Anytime.
I accept your challenge.
But not a child's game.
I challenge you to a game of real football.
Football? I...
You've always been a coward.
When you want.
A Time!
A game without a bet?
Let's make this interesting.
If Amadeo win, you return
in the city.
What? Are you afraid?
Hello!
Want to play a game in the new stadium?
- Sure. Against who?
-The Absolutes.
Want to show me how to play
football?
Horrible. Weak. Lazy.
Go take five.
We have to play psychologically,
because they will kill us physically.
Want to...
- Play...
- Football?
Accepted then?
- Sure.
Hate. Hatred. Hatred.
Amadeo.
Look. I have a candidate.
Laucha,
say that is the fastest in town.
- Is true?
- I borrow a pencil?
What...
He's not going anywhere.
You are in my custody.
And not to watch him in the field?
What a surprise, Amadeo.
Need of God's forgiveness?
No, Father, I need a quarterback
and content myself with a priest.
I can not return to the city until the
Helpless Sports
win the Copa Libertadores.
A promise is a promise.
Do not know what happened?
The Absolutes bought the Sport Helpless.
Ended up with the field
and built a megashopping.
Not!
A player missing for us
and no more men in the city. Ideas?
I have an idea.
Thank you for joining the team, but
could not shave his face until Sunday?
I have a question.
Do not know if we play 4-4-2 or 4-3-3.
Beto If I were you, it would play 11-0.
The eleven would lock in
to prevent goals.
Amadeo.
They will kill us.
Go to 20, 30 goals.
What an exaggeration.
- Maybe ten or 15.
- They are stars.
We are terrible.
- You are the best I know.
- In foosball. Do not understand?
We are not real players.
You, Bob and I mostly.
Do not worthless.
They are real. We are toys.
Hey, what's going on?
None.
Like nothing? Crying.
I'm not.
I was studying the topic
monoculture. Only pasture.
If not for me,
would not have happened, Amadeo.
What are you talking about?
This. All this.
The Bar, the city, the challenge.
What is the challenge?
As you have? Will slaughter us.
We will lose everything.
Will score a thousand goals.
You have very little faith.
Not seen the team that set up?
Not seen in training?
's Why.
Not imagine how were the last days.
In both killed in train.
But you are amateurs.
But we bet the city.
They do not bet anything.
Laurita,
trust me.
Turn on the light tower
You do not know your name.
Do not want to know.
Light! That one. The other
Light
Tomorrow.
Never seen anyone with as
much control of the game.
I was good, no?
I was not talking about you.
Welcome to the inaugural match of the
largest stadium in the world,
Universal Astro
Absolutes powerful...
Come on, guys.
We have the latest technology.
1300 cameras, 800 cranes, 200 satellites.
One step too much to ask?
Must be joking! What is your name?
- Juan José
- There'll call your name.
Introduce the players before the king fret.
Fernando Mendiguiri,
Sebastien Dubigny,
Badara Bubaye, Nicola Sampietro,
McAntony Benjamin, Ahmed Assaidi, Ayrton
Andrade,
Mohamed Yasar and in goal,
Hosam Said, Patrik Van der Luvin,
and incomparable Ezekiel
Remacho EI Grosso
referee Tristoforo Bomberini
Armando Ferrero Demosthenes
Father Jose Leguizamon
Laucha Vicente Navarro
in goal,
Carmino Bienaventurado Loprete .
Luis  "Emo" Kracorian
Eusebio Daniel Quintana
Subdelegate Bautista Pisano
Claudio Alcides Peter Juvenal
"Dual Axis" Rodriguez
Evaristo "Bark" Cuevas
Hormone Dominguez .
Amadeo Gonzalez
ELSA OF LINGERIE BRA OF YOUR LIFE
- What are you doing?
- I went, everyone does.
Seems that gives good luck.
And the game begins
Bark Cuevas swing
for Amadeo, who returns to Ferrero
Ferrero switches to Dominguez Hormone,
I was not paying attention
Dual Axis curses and begs
and he finally reacts
- It passes Quintana and...
- Son, here
- Here!
- The priest appears on the left
- Father!
- Shooting in the middle!
- Pass the ball!
- Kick!
- Two short and long?
A long pass to Gonzalez .
McAntony steals the ball effortlessly
Pass Sampietro
Pass Van der Luvin,
again in the middle to Assaidi,
and Bubaye comes into play
Beautiful feint to the
priest and Kracorian
He kicks the ball
The ball is deflected
You can leave!
Not caught.
Goal
EI brand Grosso 1 O
before the first minute . playing
Come on, guys!
We still have 89 minutes and a half.
Amadeo to Cueva Cueva for Ferrero
Ferrero to Laucha, which is free
Laucha boots .
Wait! Where have you seen?
Subdelegado knocks him
And prepares to counter attack
Said gives a high kick and long
Bubaye gets the ball and goes with
Kracorian Emo
What a moment for the Absolute :
EI Grosso dribbles
Dribbles fine,
kicks rabona
Go over to Bubaye
In trave! What miracle
You can leave!
- Drop! What are you doing?
- Wax!
- But we are losing!
- Only 1-0.
- Are not listening to me.
- Take it easy.
All week planning the game and
look what they are doing.
Here, Eusebio!
Eusebio kicks looking Amadeo
Thick intercepts the pass
unhappy and moves with the ball
Pass by Ferrero
Manda  the ball right in the
middle of the beams .
The time judge!
Goal EI Grosso
Please! That chicken
Goal!
No, it's too easy.
The game is a massacre.
- It's not funny.
- Superchato.
What are you doing?
What? I am destroying them.
Do not destroy them so easily.
No suspense.
So what? 'll Detonate them with goals.
Has the second time for this.
Dance a little. Have fun.
Do not forget that, after all,
this is a business.
This is sin, your pet.
Not touch him. Was the ball.
Double Axle, okay?
Bob does not know this situation well.
Bob only knows the triumph,
glory and applause.
No words   this.
I'm speechless.
How do you say when you
are ready for anything?
How do you say when the
rules do not matter?
What matters is friendship,
your city, defend.
And I, do not forget me.
How do you say when you know
that there is only one option?
Winning.
How do you say?
You say
Passion!
Guys! They need us!
Follow me.
Bubaye advances
Is a nightmare for the
midfield local time
Bubaye has the ball
And she goes by the priest Leguizamon
seems that goal will be
Bubaye inexplicably falls
Calm. It's okay
The game is over.
Began the war.
Absolutes advance again
Emo recovers the ball
Come on!
McAntony gets the ball and passes to
EI Grosso
Wait! Here he comes with the ball
Hold on. He prepares the kick
Will be a firing squad,
a run, a massacre
EI Grosso prepares the shot.
The defense is not set
Not have as goalkeeper catches .
Amazing, he deflected the ball
with his right hand
In trave
Was fantastic
He defended very well
You're useless.
Local time of the right
in another attempt to
cross the midfield
Dual Axis kicks the ball.
He sends the ball into orbit
Wow! Look!
Who knew we'd get so high?
Capi! I can not return to the foosball.
Well, let us now!
The ball falls the action continues
Assaidi prepares for Halter
0  which was
Lift!
Go back to the game! Coward.
Forget about scoring foul. Continue.
Here are thanks to me.
Never forget that.
Attention! Laucha Navarro
steals the ball
It passes Cuevas.
Mendigur ¡steals the ball
Wait! Mendiguri commits
an amateur mistake
Navarro makes a feint. Pass
in the middle to Emo
Lack of EI Grosso
What a pity! For the first time,
local team comes close
What? Will not give the yellow card?
Should arrest him.
- Not booked!
- Amadeo!
Amadeo kicks the ball
The ball passes through the barrier
Going toward the goal.
Easily Ball for Said
Goal! Amazing!
Yes, Goal!
Goal of the city
Amadeo Gonzalez brand of free kick
An inexplicable error by keeper
Okay, Cordobes?
It was horrible, brother.
Let's not get overconfident.
Is only the beginning.
Come on! Bunch of useless.
EI Grosso initiating the move
- What are you doing?
-A disagreement with Assaidi
Eusebio takes the ball
Assaidi goes behind
Eusebio send to front
and avoids McAntony
Ayrton loses the ball.
The Bark gets the ball
It is covered by Dubigny.
Laucha appears out of nowhere.
Do not let it go.
Laucha to Amadeo. What danger
Mendiguri knocks him
Amadeo.
What are you doing here?
Nicely, Amadeo.
We take care of everything.
Malparittis has a terrible barbed wire.
Not!
Do not want to cheat.
Are you crazy?
Not realize that the city will lose?
Let's win and do it right.
Go lose! The city, Laura.
We will win!
With that team?
Therewith.
Take!
Guys! Get off the field!
Hormone catches the ball.
Moves to Armando
Laucha gets the ball
Goal
Goal!
Goal of the city
Local time leveler
With a beautiful shot
of Emo Kracorian
What a thrilling
exciting That
- How long?
- Seven more minutes.
- Seven.
What happened? Not seen. How much longer?
Seven more minutes. Drop me.
Local time heading for victory
Attention! Carmino and advocacy
abandon her and run to attack
The city is bold :
From new to Amadeo
Laucha the right.
Mingled Time
Laucha gun
Risk score. In the middle and score
Amadeo
was the beam
Would be the winning goal
EI Grosso fouls in Amadeo,
but the referee does not see.
Penalty was
But the judge orders to continue
Amadeo tries to reach him
The crowd does not believe in endgame
He enters the small area
and Amadeo can not stop Io
not going to get stop it
Grosso goal. Grosso goal
Calm, Capi! Listen to what is happening.
Whatever I Hear?
There is no sound.
Exact Capi!
I won!
Goal!
I won! Goal!
- Amadeo, Amadeo!
- I won!
Amadeo! Amadeo.
Lost.
No matter, Amadeo.
Who are applauding?
Have to applaud me.
They saw that I won?
I'm sorry.
But the public wants something different.
Idiot! There are screaming my name!
Why do I pay you?
No more pay me. I quit.
What? It is nothing without me.
I'm the ruler. I am the star.
I am the idol.
Astros fade.
Idols fall.
Maiorais age.
Entrepreneurs are eternal.
I'd give you my shirt, but it is painted.
I love you,... Color Claret Wine.
Friendship!
Football is amazing!
And a box of surprises
Not ask me how or why
But the local team managed
to get into the game
and played as equals
against Absolute
And what happened?
The residents chose to create a new city
instead of living in the city of Grosso.
What happened to Amadeo?
He just wanted to be the hero of Laurita.
Then got married and had a son.
A beautiful son.
Do not believe any of it.
Foosball players.
Who will believe that?
I tell you a true story.
Believe it.
These players even exist?
Are they alive?
Father! Can I see them?
Believe and you will see.
I didn't hit you. It's a tattoo.
- That Tattoo?
- A Tattoo!
So it seems I have tattoo.
-Foul!
- Foul
Looks like a ballerina.
13 meters, Amadeo.
- Amadea Amadeo.
-He has a tattoo, Amadeo.
It's time, Son. Come on.
They are winning 2-1, but
we can turn the game.
You know football.
Anything can happen.
Come. Let's play.